[Music]
[âm nhạc]
v k v k Summer is here, everywhere is bustling with
v k v k mua hé tới nơi nơi rộn ràng niềm
new joy, a little bit of volunteering, we are ready to
vui mới hơi ttin nguyện viên nào ta sẵn
go. Let's go, let's call, let's call, our hearts are filled with joy, our hearts are
sàng đi Thôi về kêu về kêu lòng rốn vui
already empty. Dragon, let's go to the summer camp, so many
tim đã mờ Rồng cho đ kho tu mùa hè ngần
days of happiness. Let's say goodbye to worries. It's
ngày ch Hy đến đâ tạm biệt âu lo B khôn
hard to come to the camp, the worries are gone. All
khó đến khoa tu muộn phiền Tan biế Bao
the love is in the camp, goodbye, let's go
tình thương ở kho t tạm biệt ph ta cùng
together to the camp, thousands of loving
nhau đến khoa t ngàn tình thương mên
hands reaching out to the camp. Oh, students, through the
giang tay đ khóa Sinh ơi trẳng qua năng
rain, we must stay awake all night, always
mưa gi phải thức trong suốt đêm luôn s
side by side, the love is always given, always
cánh bên nhau tình huyền viên luôn hết
striving, the value is
mình sức luên rè được tr giá PH
for the future, for the bright future.
vì tương lai gi ngi vì Việ n sáng tươi
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
V, calling v, calling, summer is here, everywhere is bustling with
V kêu v kêu mua hết tới nơi nơi dọn ràng
new joy, a little bit of volunteering,
niềm vui mới hy ình nguyện viên nh ta
let's be ready. V, calling v, calling, our hearts are filled with joy, our hearts are already empty, welcoming the summer camp, thousands of loving hands reaching out to the camp. Goodbye to worries, all the worries are in the camp, we are ready to welcome the summer camp, thousands of loving hands reaching out to the camp. Oh, students, through the rain, we must stay awake all night. Let's go.
hãy sẵn sàng V kêu v kêu lò dỗi vui tim
Goodbye to worries, all the worries are gone, we are ready to come.
ngạ chi hay đến đây Tạm biệt âu lo bao
All the
côn kh đến khoa t muốn viên Tan Biến bao
love is in the camp, let
tình thương ở khoa
's go together to the camp,
T Tam biết phô xa ta cùng nhau đến khoa
thousands of loving hands reaching out to welcome the camp. Oh, students,
tu ngăn tình thư mế dàng tay đón khóa xh
through the rain, we must stay awake all night.
ơi trẳng qua năm mưa d phải thức trong
Throughout the night, we're always side by side, little one. Huyen
suốt đêm luôn sát cánh bé nhau ình Huyền
Vien always gives her all, always strives for
viên luôn hết mình gi sức luên rè đứ tr
enlightenment, for the future, for a
giác phân đà vì tương lai giáng ngơi vì
bright and prosperous Vietnam.
Việt Nam sáng tươi
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
It's not that we have to stay awake all
chẳng qu năng mưa d phải thức Trang suốt
night, Trang always stays side by side. Together, the love between us. Huyen Vien
đêm luôn s cánh Đơi nhau tình D viên
always gives her all, always strives for enlightenment,
luôn m s sức luên r Đức Trí gi phật đà
for the future, for Vietnam.
vì tương lai Giang lời vì Việ Nam
La La La La La
x La La
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
[Applause]
[Vỗ tay]
I
I
[Music]
[âm nhạc]